So guys, watch this video till the end if
you want to crack the interview of ICICI
Aspire Program.  Hello guys, welcome back
to my channel with another new video.  And this
video is best on ICICI Aspire Program
2025.  Look,
I have already made a video on all its basic details.  You
can go there and watch my video.  If you are
new to this program and have any
doubts about it, please tell me in the comment box.
I have already cleared all your doubts
in my previous video, so
you can go and watch that video also.  So, generally
a very common doubt came to me that ma'am the
exam has been cleared but we have to
prepare for the interview.  So what kind of
questions will we be asked in the interview
?
Tell me about the questions that will be asked.  So I have made this video especially
for you people in which
I will tell you
which questions will be asked to you in the interview.  So
I have prepared a list of 16 such questions
for all of you.  If you prepare these 16 questions
properly.  So I
bet you that you will crack your interview easily.
If you want to get
selected.  So prepare these questions
properly.
You will definitely be selected.  Ok?  So let's
start this video.  But before that, don't
forget to like this video and subscribe to the channel
so that you don't miss any upcoming
internship, job and career related
videos.  So, let's
start this video without wasting much more
time.  So guys, the first question is tell me about yourself.
Definitely
you go to any interview.  So this is the first
question.  Make sure that
you
go properly prepared on how to answer it.  Ok?  A
second question is that if you have
taken a gap in your career then they can ask you
why you have taken the gap and
you will have to tell the reason for it.  So make sure that
you go prepared for that too.  The third
question is very important in which they
can ask you why do you want
to join ICICI Bank and why do you want
to join the banking sector?  The fourth question is
what is sales?  Definitely a sales
job.  So you will be asked about the
sales?  So make sure that you
go properly prepared for this also.  The sixth
question will be how you will perform the
sales job.  The seventh question is, how will you
identify the customers and how will you sell
the products and services to the customers of
ICI Bank.  The eight questions will be for which
profile have you applied?  Definitely you
have to apply for Relationship Manager because the
program is based on Relationship Manager
only.  So, you have to answer it
properly, right?  And definitely if you have
answered this question as Relationship Manager.
So, the next question will be
based on that.  It will be related to that.
So, the ninth question will be what is
relationship manager and explain the role and
responsibilities of a relationship manager
in a bank.  10th question will be, why do
you want to join ICICI Bank?  Make
sure that you answer it in a very professional
manner.  Its answer
is given very well on Google.  Make sure that you
go there prepared.  The 11th question they
will ask you is what is RBI?  What are
the roles and responsibilities of
RBI?  So the 12th question will be what do
you know about the banking products and
services?  13 Question will be What is
repo rate?  What is Reserve Repo Rate?   The
question is different.  They will ask you, are
you comfortable in relocation?  If you
say yes or no, then make
sure that you answer this question with your proper reason.
15th question will be
based on your location, what is your location
?  So you make sure that you
explain it properly.  16 Questions will
be What is a secured loan?  What is
Unsecured Loan?  So make sure that you
go after proper preparation for this also.  So guys these
were some 16 questions and definitely you will be asked questions
on these 16 questions in
an interview round.  So make sure
that you prepare all 16 questions before
going.  Right?  If I may
give you a small conclusion.  So generally
you will be asked very easy questions in this interview.
Tell me about yourself, your
educational background, your family
background.  So definitely you should
go for this only after making proper preparation.
You are preparing for the next ICICI Bank.
The questions will be based on ICICI Bank.
So make sure that before the interview you
check all his history and details
related to the bank.  Ok?  And some questions will be
asked from you related to banking sector and banking products.  And make sure that
you take complete information related to banking also.
Whatever banking terms there are.
Right?  Make sure that you read it completely and
go prepared.  If you go prepared with these
questions and the conclusion I have given.
So I
bet you that you will crack your interview easily.
And a common doubt came to me that
ma'am, what will be the language of the interview
?  It will be in Hindi or English.
So let me tell you, nothing like this has been mentioned on the website
about the language.
So last year I asked a student and
he gave his interview
in Hindi language.  But he was
asked a question, tell me about your
location in English.  So make sure that you
go prepared in English language also because if your interview is being conducted
in Hindi then they can ask you one or two
questions in English language also.
So make sure that you
go prepared in both the languages ​​and I
hope your interview is the best.  I
hope you found this video very valuable.
All your friends and
relatives who are preparing for this program
or have been selected for the interview, go and
prepare all these questions properly.  And I bet
you that you will crack this interview easily.
So guys, if you liked the video very much
, found it valuable, then don't forget to
like and subscribe to the channel.  And if you have any kind
of doubts, ask me in the
comment box.  I will definitely respond to
your doubts.  So guys, see you
in the next video for the next update.